<!-- This is used to install the plugin as an add-on:
https://www.oxygenxml.com/doc/versions/18.1/ug-editor/topics/packing-and-deploying-addons.html#packing-and-deploying-addons
 -->
<xt:extensions xmlns:xt="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension/extensions.xsd">
    <xt:extension xmlns:xt="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension"
        id="com.oxygenxml.translation.support.TranslationPackageBuilderPlugin">
        <xt:location href="https://github.com/oxygenxml/Translation-Package-Builder/releases/download/${project.version}/${project.build.finalName}-plugin.jar"/>
        <xt:version>${project.version}</xt:version>
        <xt:oxy_version>19.0+</xt:oxy_version>
        <xt:type>plugin</xt:type>
        <xt:author>Syncro Soft SRL</xt:author>
        <xt:name>DITA Translation Package Builder</xt:name>
        <xt:description><html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
            <head>
                <title>DITA Translation Package Builder</title>
            </head>
            <body>
                <div>
                    <p>This plugin is a helper for sending DITA files to translation. It contributes a sub-menu
                        named "Translation Package Builder" in the <b>DITA Maps Manager</b>'s contextual menu. The 
                        actions present in this group are: </p>
                    <ol>
                        <li><b>Generate Milestone</b> - this action is the first one to use. It will generate an unique hash 
                            for each documentation resource. This information will be used by the second action to detect which files 
                            have been modified. A milestone file should be generated the first time you install this plugin and, afterwards,
                            after each package sent to translators.</li>
                        <li><b>Create Modified Files Package</b> - this action detects which files have been
                            changed since the last generated milestone. These files are packed insdie a ZIP
                            file that can be send to translators. After doing this you can also generate a
                            new milestone so that the next package will contain just the new changes.<p>This
                                action also creates a report with the modified resources
                                (<b>modified_resources_report.xhtml</b>). If your translation agency is
                                DITA-aware you can opt to send him the entire DITA project together with
                                this report.</p></li>
                        <li><b>Apply Package</b> - when  the translated files arrive from the translator you should open the DITA map
                            that corresponds to the received language (open dita-map-french.ditamap if the package contains the french translation). 
                            Invoking this action will extract the changed files inside map's directory.</li>
                    </ol>
                    
                </div>
                <h1>Release Notes 1.0.9</h1>
                <ul>
                    <li>XML files are scanned for changes <a href="https://github.com/oxygenxml/oxygen-dita-translation-package-builder/issues/18">#18</a></li>
                    <li>Small UI changes.</li>
                </ul>
                <h1>Release Notes 1.0.8</h1>
                <ul>
                    <li>Milestones are now generated based on the DITA Map structure. The resources referred
                        in the map will be scanned for changes. <a
                            href="https://github.com/oxygenxml/Translation-Package-Builder/issues/8"
                            >#8</a></li>
                    <li>References to missing resources will be reported in oXygen's Results Manager but the
                        packaging process will continue.<a
                            href="https://github.com/oxygenxml/Translation-Package-Builder/issues/14"
                            >#14</a></li>
                    <li>In some cases the milestone report contained duplicate and invalid data, preventing
                        the creation of the package.<a
                            href="https://github.com/oxygenxml/Translation-Package-Builder/issues/15"
                            >#15</a></li>
                    <li>The root map was not added in the milestone even if it was modified.<a
                        href="https://github.com/oxygenxml/Translation-Package-Builder/issues/16"
                        >#16</a></li>
                    <li>The generated XHTML report that contains the relative paths of the modified
                        resources is now valid and the referred resources are sorted alphabetically.<a
                            href="https://github.com/oxygenxml/Translation-Package-Builder/issues/17"
                            >#17</a>
                    </li>
                </ul>
                <p>For more details, please visit the project location: 
                    <a href="https://github.com/oxygenxml/oxygen-dita-translation-package-builder">
                        https://github.com/oxygenxml/oxygen-dita-translation-package-builder</a></p>
            </body>
        </html>
        </xt:description>
        <xt:license>            
            Copyright 2018 Syncro Soft SRL
            
            Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
            you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
            You may obtain a copy of the License at
            
            http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
            
            Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
            distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
            WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
            See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
            limitations under the License.
        </xt:license>
    </xt:extension>
</xt:extensions>


