<!-- This is used to install the plugin as an add-on:
https://www.oxygenxml.com/doc/versions/18.1/ug-editor/topics/packing-and-deploying-addons.html#packing-and-deploying-addons
 -->
<xt:extensions xmlns:xt="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension/extensions.xsd">
    <xt:extension xmlns:xt="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension"
        id="com.oxygenxml.translation.support.TranslationPackageBuilderPlugin">
        <xt:location href="${project.build.finalName}-plugin.jar"/>
        <xt:version>${project.version}</xt:version>
        <xt:oxy_version>17.0+</xt:oxy_version>
        <xt:type>plugin</xt:type>
        <xt:author>Oxygen XML Editor</xt:author>
        <xt:name>Translation Package Builder</xt:name>
        <xt:description><html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
            <head>
                <title>Translation Package Builder</title>
            </head>
            <body>
                <div>
                    <p>This plugin is a helper for sending DITA files to translation. It contributes a sub-menu
                        named "Translation Package Builder" in the <b>DITA Maps Manager</b>'s contextual menu. The 
                    actions present in this group are: </p>
                    <ol>
                        <li><b>Generate Milestone</b> - this action is the first one to use. It will generate an unique hash 
                        for each documentation resource. This information will be used by the second action to detect which files 
                        have been modified. A milestone file should be generated the first time you install this plugin and, afterwards,
                        after each package sent to translators.</li>
                        <li><b>Create Modified Files Package</b> - this action detects which files have been changed since the last
                        generated milestone. These files are packed insdie a ZIP file that can be send to translators. After doing this
                        you can also generate a new milestone so that the next package will contain just the new changes.</li>
                        <li><b>Apply Package</b> - when  the translated files arrive from the translator you should open the DITA map
                        that corresponds to the received language (open dita-map-french.ditamap if the package contains the french translation). Invoking this action will extract the changed files inside 
                        the map's directory.</li>
                    </ol>
                    
                </div>
            </body>
        </html>
        </xt:description>
        <xt:license><![CDATA[(c) Syncro Soft , All rights reserved.
This Plug-In is part of the Oxygen XML Software and, as such, is part of the License Agreement governing the Oxygen XML Software.
]]></xt:license>
    </xt:extension>
</xt:extensions>


