<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<third-party>
    <component id="org.slf4j:slf4j-api:1.7.32" product="editor author">
        <name>SLF4J API Module</name>
        <version>1.7.32</version>
        <project-info>
            <about>The Simple Logging Facade for Java (SLF4J) library serves as a simple facade or 
				abstraction for various logging frameworks (e.g. java.util.logging, logback, log4j) 
				allowing the end user to plug in the desired logging framework at deployment time.
				The library was modified by Syncro Soft SRL for adding extra methods to the facade.</about>
            <licensor>QOS.ch</licensor>
            <start-year>2005</start-year>
            <project-url>http://www.slf4j.org</project-url>
        </project-info>
        <license>
            <type>MIT License</type>
            <content> Copyright (c) 2004-2017 QOS.ch
 All rights reserved.

 Permission is hereby granted, free  of charge, to any person obtaining
 a  copy  of this  software  and  associated  documentation files  (the
 "Software"), to  deal in  the Software without  restriction, including
 without limitation  the rights to  use, copy, modify,  merge, publish,
 distribute,  sublicense, and/or sell  copies of  the Software,  and to
 permit persons to whom the Software  is furnished to do so, subject to
 the following conditions:
 
 The  above  copyright  notice  and  this permission  notice  shall  be
 included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.
 
 THE  SOFTWARE IS  PROVIDED  "AS  IS", WITHOUT  WARRANTY  OF ANY  KIND,
 EXPRESS OR  IMPLIED, INCLUDING  BUT NOT LIMITED  TO THE  WARRANTIES OF
 MERCHANTABILITY,    FITNESS    FOR    A   PARTICULAR    PURPOSE    AND
 NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE
 LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION
 OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE,  ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION
 WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.</content>
            <url>http://www.slf4j.org/license.html</url>
        </license>
    </component>
</third-party>